Sanctuary Movement Trial papers, 1979-1992
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 4: "A" Files, ca. 1985
  - Leon-Cabrera, Dora Angelica de, no date (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Lopez, Elba Teresa, no date (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Lopez, Maria Teresa, no date (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Mancia-Segovia, Jose Noe, no date (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Martinez, Juan, no date (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Martinez, Luis, no date (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Martinez, Matilde, no date (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Martinez-Chavez, Pompeyo, no date (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Martinez-Palacios, Silver Isaac, no date (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Martel-Reyes, Francisco, no date (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Meda-Gonzalez, Fidel, no date (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Mejia-Barrera, Miguel Angel, no date (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mejia, Miguel Angel, no date (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Morales-Arrecis, Luz Johanna, no date (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Nieto-Nunez, Francisco, no date (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Nunez-Villatoro, Candida, no date (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Nunez-Villator, Candida Natalia, no date (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Ortiz-Cabrera, Fidel, no date (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Pascual-Gaspar, Gabriel, no date (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Pineda-Martel, Luis Alberto, no date (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Quinones-Najaro, Alvaro, no date (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Recinos-Calderon, Jose Antonio, no date (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Rodriguez-Martel, Sergio, no date (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Sanchez-Albarenga, Maria del Carmen, no date (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Sandoval-Rivas, Gloria E., no date (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Sanzo-Garay, Julio Joaquin, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Segovia, Jose Noe, no date (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Segovia-Mancia, Maria Isabel, no date (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Toledo-Juarez de Cruz, Ana, no date (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Valenti, Edwin, no date (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Ballentty, Siomarn, no date (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Vargas-Lanaverde, Maria, no date (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Vittatoro, Martha Argentina, no date (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Villeda, Juan Jose, no date (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Villeda-Lemos, Jose, no date (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Villeda-Lemos, Sonia, no date (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Zelaya-Ticas, Sonia, no date (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Zenito-J, no date (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Statements, no date (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Series 5: Count Files, no date
  - Count # 1, no date (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Count # 2, no date (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Count # 3, no date (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Count # 4, no date (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Count # 5, no date (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Count # 6, no date (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Count # 7, no date (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Count # 8, no date (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Count # 9, no date (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Count # 10, no date (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Count # 11, no date (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Count # 12, no date (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Count # 13, no date (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Count # 14, no date (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Count # 15 (part 1), no date (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Count # 15 (part 2), nodate (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Count # 16, no date (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Count # 17, no date (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Count # 18, no date (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Count # 19, no date (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Count # 20, no date (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Count # 21, no date (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Count # 22, no date (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Count # 23, no date (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Count # 24, no date (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Count # 25, no date (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Count # 26, no date (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Count # 27, no date (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Count # 28, no date (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Count # 29, no date (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Count # 30, no date (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Count # 31, no date (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Count # 32, no date (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Count # 33, no date (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Count # 34, no date (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Count # 35, no date (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Count # 36, no date (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Count # 37, no date (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Count # 38, no date (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Count # 39, no date (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Count # 40, no date (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Count # 41, no date (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Count # 42, no date (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Count # 43, no date (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Count # 44, no date (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Count # 45, no date (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Count # 46, no date (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Count # 47, no date (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Count # 48, no date (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Count # 49, no date (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Count # 50, no date (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Count # 51, no date (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Count # 52, no date (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Count # 53, no date (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Count # 54, no date (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Count # 55, no date (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Count # 56, no date (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Series 6: Trial Notebooks, ca. 1985
  - Trial Notebook--part one, no date (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Trial Notebook--part two, no date (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Trial Notebook--Alien deportation papers, no date (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Trial Notebook--Clippings, no date (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Trial Notebook--Clippings, no date (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Trial Notebook--Conger, Phil (part one), no date (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Trial Notebook--Conger, Phil (part two), no date (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Trial Notebook--Conger, Phil (part three), no date (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Trial Notebook--Correspondence, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Trial Notebook--Cruz, Jesus--Cross Examination (part one), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Trial Notebook--Cruz, Jesus--Cross Examination (part two), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Trial Notebook--Cruz, Jesus--Cross Examination (part three), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Trial Notebook--Defendants & Unindicted co-conspirators, no date (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Trial Notebook--Jury Instructions (part one), no date (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Trial Notebook--Jury Instructions (part two), no date (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Trial Notebook--Jury Instructions (part three), no date (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Trial Notebook--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene (part one), no date (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Trial Notebook--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene (part two) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Trial Notebook--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene (part three), no date (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Trial Notebook--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Trial Notebook--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Trial Notebook--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Trial Notebook--Subpoenas Affidavits (part one), no date (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Trial Notebook--Subpoenas Affidavits (part two), no date (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Trial Notebook--Subpoenas Affidavits (part three), no date (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Trial Notebook--Subpoenas Affidavits (part four), no date (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Trial Notebook--Sanctuary Movement (part one), March-July 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Trial Notebook--Sanctuary Movement (part two), March-July 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Trial Notebook--Sanctuary Movement (part three), March-July 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Trial Notebook--Sanctuary Movement (part four), March-July 1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Trial Notebook--Sanctuary Movement (part one), August-September 1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Trial Notebook--Sanctuary Movement (part two), August-September1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Trial Notebook--Sanctuary Movement (part three), August-September 1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Trial Notebook--Sanctuary Movement (part four), August-September 1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Series 7: Trial Transcripts, 1985-1986
  - Subseries 1: Pre-trial transcripts, January-October 1985
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 1, January-February1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 2, May 21, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 3 (part one), May 22, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 3 (part two), May 22,1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 4 (part one), May 23, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 4 (part two), May 23, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 5, May 24, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 6 (part one), June 25, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 6 (part two), June 25,1985 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 7 (part one), June 26, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 7 (part two), June 26,1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 8 (part one), July-October 1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Pre-trial motions, vol. 8 (part two), July-October 1985 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Pre-trial interviews--Dunlap, Arthur K., June 7, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Pre-trial interviews--Chase, Charles A., Jr., June 8, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Pre-trial interviews--Coffin, Robert S., June 8, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Pre-trial interviews--Cruz, Jesus, June 8, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Pre-trial interviews--Reed, Mark Kevin, June 7,1985 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Pre-trial interviews--Rayburn, James, June 8,1985 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Pre-trial interviews--Graham, Salomon, June 8, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Motions (re: openings), November 20,1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Opening Statements, November 15, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Closing Arguments, April 3,1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2: Depositions, September, 1984
    - Ana, September 14, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Bourgeois, Philippe, September 19, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Calderon, Ricardo, September 14,1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Canales, Epifanio, September 19, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Clements, Charles, September 20, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Coatsworth, John, September 17, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Cozette, Gary, September 18, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Cruz, Valentin, September 19, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Duignan, Sister Maureen, September 14, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Ford, William P., September 19, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Forche, Caroline, September 20, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Funes, Rudy, September 17, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Goldman, Robert, September 21, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Hector, September 18, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Hoff, Anna M., no date (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Leo Grande, William, September 21, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Mattison, Henry, September 4, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Mendez, Juan, September 21, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Montgomery, Tommie Sue, September 21, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Neier, Aryeh, September 4, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Parker, Karen, September 14, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Ramirez, Secundino, September 18, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Rone, Jemera, September 4, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Solorzano, Jesus, September 17, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Suzanne, September 18, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Subseries 3: "Operation Sojourner,", ca. 1985
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts and notes, no date (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Operation Sojourner--court orders, November 6, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts, 1-6, no date (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - OOperation Sojourner--transcripts 7-11, no date (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 12-16, no date (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 17-22, no date (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 23-25, no date (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 26-28, no date (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 29-34, no date (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 35-40, no date (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 41-43, no date (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 44-46, no date (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 47-50, no date (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcript 51, no date (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 52-54, no date (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 55-60, no date (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 61-64, no date (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 65-67, no date (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 68-75, no date (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 76-80, no date (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 81-83, no date (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 84-85, no date (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 86, no date (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Operation Sojourner--transcripts 87-91, no date (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Operation Sojourner--Summaries of Transcripts, no date (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Operation Sojourner--Unnumbered Transcripts, no date (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 4: Certified Trial Transcripts, October 1985-May 1986
    This series contains restricted material. Transcripts in box 20, folder 15 and box 21, folder 9 and 14 are sealed by court order.
    - Grand Jury Indictments, no date (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 1, October 22, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 2 (part one), October 23, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 2 (part two), October 23, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 3 (part one), October 24, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 3 (part two), October 24, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 4 (part one), October 25, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 4 (part two), October 25, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 5, October 29, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 6 (part one), October 30, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 6 (part two), October 30, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 7 (part one), October 31, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 7 (part two), October 31, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 8 (part one), November 1, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 8 (part two), November 1, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 9, November 4, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 10, November 5, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 11, November 6, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 12, November 7, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 13, November 8, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 14 (part one), November 12, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 14 (part two), November 12, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 15, November 13, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 16, November 14, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 17 (part one), November 15, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 17 (part two), November 15, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 18 (part one), November 19, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 18 (part two), November 19, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 19 (part one), November 20, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 19 (part two), November 20, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 20, November 21, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 21, November 22, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 22 (part one), November 25, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 22 (part two), November 25, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 23, November 26, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 24, December 3, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 25, December 4, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 26, December 5, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 27, December 6, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 28 (part one), December 10, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 28 (part two), December 10, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 29, December 11, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 30, December 12, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 31, December 13, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 32, December 17, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 33, December 18, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 34, December 19, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 35, December 20, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 36, January 7, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 37, January 8, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 38, January 9, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 39, January 10, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 40, January 14, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 41, January 15, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 42, January 16, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 43, January 17, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 44, January 21, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 45, January 22, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - (Restricted) Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 46-47, January 23, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 48, January 29, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 49, January 30,1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 50, January 31, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 51, February 4, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 52, February 5, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 53, February 6, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 54, February 7, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 55, February 11, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - (Restricted) Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 56, February 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 57, February 13, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 58, February 15, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 59, February 18, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 60, February 19, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - (Restricted) Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 61, February 20, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 62, February 21, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 63, February 25, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 64, February 26, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 65, February 27, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 66, February 28, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 67 (part one), March 4, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 67 (part two), March 4, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 68, March 5, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 69, March 6, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 70, March 7, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 71, March 11, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 72, March 12, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 73, March 13, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 74-75, March 14, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 76, March 19, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 77, March 20, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 78, March 21, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 79, March 25, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 80, March 26, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 81, March 31, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 82, April 1, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 83, April 2, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 84, April 3, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 85, April 4, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 86, April 8, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 87, April 9,1986 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 88, April 10,1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 89, April 11, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 90, April 15, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 91 (part one), April 16, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 91 (part two), April 16, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Certified Trial Transcripts, vol. 92, April 17-May 1, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 5: Trial Summaries, January 1985-May 1986
    - Pre-trial motions, no date (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Volumes 1-8, no date (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Volumes 9-16, no date (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Volumes 17 & testimony summaries, no date (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Volumes 18-34, no date (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Volumes 35-42, no date (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Volumes 43-49, no date (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Volumes 50-55, no date (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Volumes 56-62, no date (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Volumes 63-70, no date (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 6: Post-verdict Sentencing, May-July, 1986
    - Post-verdict sentencing, vol. 1, May 16, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Post-verdict sentencing, vol. 2, June 5 & 10, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Post-verdict sentencing, vol. 3 (part one), July 1-2, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Post-verdict sentencing, vol. 3 (part two), July 1-2, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Series 8: American Friends Society Committee (AFSC) 1981-1988
  - AFSC-Arizona Sanctuary Defense Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - AFSC-Arizona Sanctuary Defense Fund-Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - AFSC-Articles, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - AFSC-Articles, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - AFSC-Articles, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - AFSC-Articles, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - AFSC-Articles, no date (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - AFSC-Background-Art/Music, no date (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - AFSC-Background-Baptist Church v. Meese, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - AFSC-Background-Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - AFSC-Background-Lawsuits, no date (Box 26, Folder 6)